jnto.org.au 2011-11-15

# Privacy Policy | Japan National Tourism Organization (JNTO)

**__PRIVACY POLICY OF JAPAN NATIONAL TOURISM ORGANISATION (“JNTO”)__**

We deal with the collection, security, quality, use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the _Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)_. If we communicate with you by email, we are also bound by the _Spam Act 2003 (Cth)_.

We also strive to handle personal information in a manner which is consistent with the local privacy laws that apply in the various international jurisdictions in which JNTO operates. 

**Collection of personal information**

The types of personal information that we collect will depend on the nature of your dealings with us.  For example, we may collect personal information directly from you when you:

-      Subscribe to any of our publications or register to receive brochures;

-      Apply to attend or exhibit at a JNTO event, or enter a promotion or competition; 

-      Have business dealings with us (whether as an employee of one of our external service providers, or if you work for any agencies or companies we deal with, or in the context of a transaction, or if you volunteer personal information to us).

We need to collect personal information so that we can provide you with the publications or services you have requested. The particular purpose for which we collect personal information will either be explained when we collect that information, or will be obvious from the context in which it is collected. 

**Use of personal information**

We must only use personal information for the particular purpose we collected it for, or for other purposes that are directly related to that purpose.  If we want to use your personal information for any other purpose we must obtain your consent. If we use your personal information to send you information by email (including e-newsletters), we will always give you an opportunity to “unsubscribe”, and we will respect your wishes. 

**Disclosure of personal information**

We make only limited disclosures of personal information.  Examples of these disclosures are explained below. 

We may share personal information that we have collected in the course of conducting trade and marketing events with other government agencies and authorities.  These government agencies and authorities include Japan Tourism Agency and supporting partners of JNTO.  Such disclosure is notified when that personal information is collected.

We may disclose personal information to external service providers (e.g. IT consultants, publishing houses) or corporate sponsors who help us operate our business.  We require those external service providers and corporate sponsors to comply with contractual privacy obligations that reflect our own strict privacy obligations under the National Privacy Principles in the _Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)_. 

We may also disclose personal information when required by law.

**Access to personal information**

You have the right to request access to any information held by JNTO, which relates to you. You also have the right to request the correction of any information which relates to you and is inaccurate. Any request for access or corrections should be advised to us in writing. 

**Online Privacy Issues**

If you use our websites, you are understood to have consented to the terms and conditions set out on our websites.  This includes consenting to the terms of this privacy policy.

In general, you can visit our websites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.  However there are times when we may need to collect personal information from you. 

For instance, if you register to receive our brochures, publications, attend an event, or participate in a competition, we may be required to collect some personal information from you.  At the time of collection, we will seek your permission to send you further electronic communications, and for your personal information to be stored in our databases. If at any time after submitting your personal information to us you have decided that you no longer like to receive information from us, simply follow the “unsubscribe” directions at the end of any email communications you receive, or contact us. 

No attempt will be made by us to identify website users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect server logs. The statistics and log files may be preserved indefinitely and used at any time and in any way necessary to prevent security breaches and to ensure the integrity of the information supplied by JNTO. 

In general on our website, IP addresses are logged to track a user’s session while the user remains anonymous. We may analyse this data for certain trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. When we receive information about your session or about you, we may also use it for research or to improve our site and the services we offer you.

**Cookies**

Some JNTO web pages use “cookies”, which are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. A cookie helps us remember who you are. Cookies can make your subsequent visits to the web page simpler and faster. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (However, by not accepting cookies, some web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.) A server cannot find out a name or email address, or anything about a user's computer, by using cookies. 

**Online Security**

We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and periodically updates its security measures in light of current technologies. 

You need to be aware of inherent risks associated with the transmission of information via the Internet.  We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any personal information you submit to our sites. If you have concerns in this regard, we have other ways of obtaining and providing information. Normal mail, telephone and fax facilities are available. 

Our website may also be linked to websites operated by third parties. These links are meant for your convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship or endorsement or approval of these sites. Visitors to those sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices

**Additional Information**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or if you wish to make a complaint about how we have handled your personal information, please contact us using the contact details below:

By Email:              travelinfo@jnto.org.au

By Post:                Suite 1, Level 4, 56 Clarence Street

                                Sydney NSW 2000 Australia

We periodically review our privacy policy, and reserve the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time.
